Every heist has its price.
Cash Out is a action, thriller film directed by Randall Emmett.
Criminal mastermind Mason is about to execute the score of a lifetime when his lover and key member of
his crew, Decker, takes the team down and reveals she’s an undercover Interpol agent.
Heartbroken, Mason escapes and retires from the life of crime until his younger brother
Shawn is out of his league taking on a big bank heist all on his own.
Mason has no choice left but to come to the rescue, while
Interpol brings Decker in hoping to unnerve him.
Before the SWAT teams storm the bank, Mason must use every tool in his arsenal to
not only escape with the prize, but also the love of his life.
Mason Goddard, played by John Travolta.
Amelia Decker, played by Kristin Davis.
Shawn Goddard, played by Lukas Haas.
Anton, played by Quavo.
Mr. Perez, played by Bernard White.
Hector, played by Noel Gugliemi.
Cash Out is a 2024 American action film directed by Ives, written by Dipo Oseni and Doug
Richardson, and starring John Travolta, Kristin Davis, Lukas Haas, and Quavo.
The film was released on April 26, 2024.
The film explores themes of police, gangster, fbi, bank heist, bank job.
The tone is intense.